Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Robert Kalmbach photograph collection 1960-2000 1969-1999
Kalmbach, Robert.
0380 Aa2
Staff photographer for University of Michigan News and Information Services and contract photographer for the University of Michigan Athletic Department. Includes negatives and contact prints of game action photos of UM athletic competitions, 1978-2000 and some personal and family photos.
27 linear feet in 62 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The photos were donated by Robert Kalmbach, 1998, negatives and contact sheets transferred through the University of Michigan Athletic Department in 2001.
No further additions to the collection expected.
The collection is open to research.
Robert Kalmbach was born in Ann Arbor, Mich., in 1934 and spent 47 years as a photographer for the University of Michigan, as a staff photographer for News and Information Services. His photographs taken in his role as News and Information Service employee are found in the News and Information Service photograph collection. Kalmbach also worked as principal contract photographer for the Athletic Department, 1969-2000. Kalmbach's pictures appeared throughout University of Michigan publications as well as Sports Illustrated, National Geographic, and the New York Times and have been reproduced in many publications on University of Michigan Athletics.
The Robert Kalmbach photograph collection consists primarily of 35mm negatives and contact sheets of University of Michigan athletic competitions and represents his work as a contract photographer for the Athletic department. He shot nearly every home football game between 1969 and 1998 and generally traveled to Notre Dame, Michigan State and Ohio State away games,. He also photographed most men's home basketball and hockey game games and several games or matches each season for other sports. His photos include some to the classic images of Michigan athletics and have been widely published in Athletic Department Media Guides, game programs and other publications.
The photos are primarily black and white, though after the mid 1980s the football photos frequently include one or more rolls of color shots. the photos are arranged by sport and thereunder chronologically by year and event. For each event the negatives have been placed in protective sleeves with matching contact sheets based on roll numbers assigned by Kalmbach. For football games (and occasionally other games) with multiple rolls, the numbering system does not always correspond to the actual sequence of the game. Some of the sports photos are identified as being taken by John Heafield, another News and Information Service photographer who occasionally worked with Kalmbach. The athletic photos are organized by sport and thereunder chronologically.
The collection also includes a small number of slides and transparencies of athletic events.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
College sports--Michigan.; Huron River (Oakland County-Monroe County, Mich.); Kalmbach, Robert.; Tahquamenon River (Mich.); University of Michigan--Basketball.; University of Michigan--Field Hockey.; University of Michigan--Football.; University of Michigan--Golf.; University of Michigan--Gymnastics.; University of Michigan--Hockey.; University of Michigan--Lacrosse.; University of Michigan--Soccer.; University of Michigan--Softball.; University of Michigan--Swimming.; University of Michigan--Tennis.; University of Michigan--Track and field.; University of Michigan--Volleyball.; University of Michigan--Wrestling.; Basketball.; Field hockey.; Football.; Golf.; Gymnastics.; Ice hockey.; Lacrosse.; Soccer.; Softball.; Swimming.; Tennis.; Track athletics.; Volleyball.; Wrestling.; Rodeos--Michigan--Saline.
Contributors:
Heafield, John.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - U-M Football photos
    - 1969
      - Vanderbilt 9/20/1969, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Washington 9/27/1969, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Missouri 10/04/1969, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Purdue 10/11/1969, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Michigan 10/18/1969, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Wisconsin 11/01/1969, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Ohio State, neg and Koadlith of team (Box 1)
        (football team on sidelines, Storey's at stadium and crowd throwing snowballs)
    - 1970
      - Arizona, Iowa, Minnesota (Box 1)
      - Michigan State 10/17/1970 (Box 1)
      - Texas A&M 10/03/1970 (Box 1)
      - Illinois 1/07/1970 (Box 1)
    - 1971
      - Virginia 9/18/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - UCLA 9/25/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Navy 10/02/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Navy 10/02/1971, slides (Box 1)
      - Illinois 10/16/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Indiana 10/30/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 1)
      - Iowa 11/06/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Ohio State 11/20/1971, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
    - 1972
      - Northwestern 9/16/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Tulane 9/30/1972, negatives, contact sheets, prints (Box 2)
      - Navy 10/07/1972, negatives, contact sheets, prints (Box 2)
      - Michigan State 10/14/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Minnesota 10/28/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Purdue 11/18/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Ohio State 11/25/1972, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
    - 1973
      - Stanford 9/22/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Navy 9/29/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Oregon 10/06/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Wisconsin 10/20/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Indiana 11/03/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Illinois 11/10/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 2)
      - Ohio State 11/24/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
    - 1974
      - Iowa 9/14/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Colorado 9/21/1974, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Navy 9/28/1974, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Michigan State 10/12/1974, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Minnesota 10/26/1974, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Purdue 11/16/1974, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Ohio State 11/23/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
    - 1975
      - Stanford 9/20/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Baylor 9/27/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Missouri 10/04/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Michigan State 10/11/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Northwestern 10/18/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Indiana 10/25/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 3)
      - Purdue 11/08/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Ohio State 11/22/1975, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
    - 1976
      - Wisconsin 9/11/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Stanford 9/18/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Navy 9/25/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Wake Forest 10/02/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Michigan State 10/09/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Minnesota 10/30/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Illinois 11/13/1976, photos, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Ohio State 11/20/1976, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
    - 1977
      - Duke 9/17/1977, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Navy 9/24/1977, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Texas A&M 10/01/1977, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Wisconsin 10/15/1977, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Iowa 10/29/1977, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Northwestern 11/05/1977, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Ohio State 11/19/1977, photos, contact sheets (Box 4)
    - 1978
      - Illinois 9/16/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Notre Dame 9/23/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 4)
      - Duke 9/30/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Arizona 10/07/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Michigan State 10/14/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Minnesota 10/28/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Purdue 11/18/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Ohio State 11/25/1978, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
    - 1979
      - Northwestern 9/08/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Notre Dame 9/15/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Kansas 9/22/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Slippery Rock 9/21/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Michigan State 10/06/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Minnesota 10/13/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Indiana 10/27/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Wisconsin 11/03/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
      - Ohio State 11/17/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 5)
    - 1980
      - Northwestern 9/13/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - South Carolina 9/27/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - California 10/04/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Michigan State 10/11/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Illinois 10/25/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Purdue 11/15/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
    - 1981
      - Notre Dame 09/19/1981, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Navy 9/26/1981, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Iowa 10/17/1981, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Northwestern 10/24/1981, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Illinois 11/07/1981, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Ohio State 11/21/1981, negatives (Box 6)
    - 1982
      - Wisconsin 9/11/1982, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - UCLA 9/25/1982, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Indiana 10/02/1982, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Michigan State 10/09/1982, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Minnesota 10/30/1982, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
      - Purdue 11/13/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 6)
    - 1983
      - Washington State 9/10/1983, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Indiana 10/01/1983, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Northwestern 10/15/1983, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Iowa 10/22/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Purdue 11/05/1983, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Ohio State 11/19/1983, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
    - 1984
      - Miami 9/08/1984, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Washington 9/15/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Wisconsin 9/22/1984, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Northwestern 10/13/1984, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Michigan State 10/06/1984, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Illinois 10/27/1984, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
      - Minnesota 11/10/1984, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 7)
    - 1985
      - Notre Dame 9/14/1985, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Maryland 9/28/1985, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Wisconsin 10/05/1985, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Indiana 10/26/1985, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Purdue 11/09/1985, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Ohio State 11/23/1985, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
    - 1986
      - Oregon State 9/20/1986, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Florida State 9/27/1986, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Michigan State 10/11/1986, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Iowa 10/18/1986, photos (Box 8)
      - Illinois 11/01/1986, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Minnesota 11/15/1986, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
    - 1987
      - Notre Dame 9/12/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Washington State 9/19/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 8)
      - Long Beach State 9/26/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Wisconsin 10/03/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Iowa 10/17/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Northwestern 10/31/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Ohio State 11/21/1987, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
    - 1988
      - Miami 9/17/1988, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Wake Forest 9/24/1988, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Michigan State 10/08/1988, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Indiana 10/22/1988, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Minnesota 11/05/1988, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Illinois 11/12/1988, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
    - 1989
      - Notre Dame 9/16/1989, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Maryland 9/30/1989, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 9)
      - Wisconsin 10/07/1989, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Indiana 10/28/1989, photos, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Purdue 11/04/1989, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
    - 1990
      - Spring Game 4/21/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - UCLA 9/22/1990, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Maryland 9/29/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Michigan State 10/15/1990, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Iowa 10/20/1990, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Illinois 11/10/1990, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Minnesota 11/17/1990, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
    - 1991
      - Notre Dame 9/14/1991, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Florida 9/28/1991, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Indiana 10/19/1991, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 10)
      - Purdue 11/02/1991, photos, negatives (Box 10)
      - Northwestern 11/09/1991, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Ohio State 11/23/1991, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
    - 1992
      - Spring Game 4/11/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Oklahoma State 9/19/1992, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Houston 9/26/1992, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Iowa 10/03/1992, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Michigan State 10/10/1992, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Minnesota 10/24/1992, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Illinois 11/14/1992, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
    - 1993
      - Spring game, negatives (Box 11)
      - Washington State 9/04/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Notre Dame 9/11/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 11)
      - Houston 9/25/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Iowa 10/02/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Illinois 10/23/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Purdue 11/06/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Ohio State 11/20/1993, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
    - 1994
      - Spring game, negatives (Box 12)
      - Boston College 9/03/1994, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Colorado 9/24/1994, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Michigan State 10/08/1994, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Penn State 10/15/1994, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Wisconsin 10/29/1994, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
      - Minnesota 11/12/1994, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 12)
    - 1995
      - Spring game, negatives (Box 13)
      - Virginia 8/29/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Memphis 9/09/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Miami of Ohio 9/30/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Northwestern 10/07/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Minnesota 10/28/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Purdue 11/11/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Ohio State 11/25/1995, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
    - 1996
      - Illinois 8/31/1996, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 13)
      - Boston College 9/21/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Boston College 9/21/1996, photos (Box 14)
      - UCLA 9/28/1996, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Indiana 10/19/1996, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Michigan State 11/02/1996, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Penn State 11/16/1996, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
    - 1997
      - Spring game, negatives (Box 14)
      - Colorado 9/13/1997, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Baylor 9/20/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Baylor 9/20/1997, photos (Box 14)
      - Notre Dame 9/21/1997, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Northwestern 10/11/1997, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Iowa 10/18/1997, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 14)
      - Minnesota 11/01/1997, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Ohio State 11/22/1997, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
    - 1998
      - Spring Game, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Notre Dame 9/05/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Syracuse 9/12/1998, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Eastern Michigan 9/19/1998, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Michigan State 9/26/1998, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Indiana 10/24/1998, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Penn State 11/07/1998, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Wisconsin 11/14/1998, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
    - 1999
      - Spring game 4/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Freshman practice 8/11/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Notre Dame 9/04/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Rice 9/11/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 15)
      - Purdue 10/02/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Michigan State 10/09/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Illinois 10/23/1999, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Lloyd Carr Show 10/23/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Northwestern 11/06/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
    - 2000
      - Wisconsin 9/30/2000, negatives (Box 16)
      - Indiana 10/14/2000, negatives (Box 16)
  - U-M Men's Basketball photos
    - 1972-1973 (Box 16)
      - Basketball 1972-1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
    - 1973-1974
      - Southern Illinois 12/01/1973, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Xavier 12/10/1973, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Indiana 1/05/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Frosh Basketball 1/05/1974, negatives (Box 16)
      - Wisconsin 1/26/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Ohio State 2/09/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Northwestern 2/11/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Minnesota 3/02/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
    - 1974-1975
      - Tennessee 12/07/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Virginia Tech 12/20/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Manhattan 12/21/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Ohio State 1/04/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Indiana 1/06/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Northwestern 1/25/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Wisconsin 1/27/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Purdue 2/01/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Michigan State 2/08/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Iowa 2/15/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Minnesota 2/17/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Illinois 3/03/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
    - 1975-1976
      - Vanderbilt 12/02/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - South Carolina 12/10/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Southern Illinois 12/19/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Miami 12/20/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Minnesota 1/05/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Indiana 1/10/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Ohio State 1/12/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Michigan State 1/17/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Iowa 1/31/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Wisconsin 2/02/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Eastern Michigan 2/16/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Purdue 2/21/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Illinois 2/23/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
      - Northwestern 3/06/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 16)
    - 1976-1977
      - Kentucky 11/27/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Fordham 12/04/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Kent State 12/18/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Wisconsin 1/08/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Wisconsin 1/08/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Purdue 1/20/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Illinois 1/22/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Northwestern 1/29/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Ohio State 2/05/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Minnesota 2/07/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Iowa 2/17/1977, color transparencies (Box 17)
      - Indiana 2/13/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Michigan State 2/26/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Marquette 3/06/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
    - 1977-1978
      - Eastern Michigan 11/30/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Louisville, 12//07/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Dayton 12/10/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Central Michigan 12/17/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Northwestern 1/05/1978, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Minnesota 1/08/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Indiana 1/26/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Purdue 1/28/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Ohio State 2/09/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Michigan State 2/11/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Illinois 2/23/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Iowa 2/25/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
    - 1978-1979
      - Windsor 11/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Central Michigan 11/30/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Alabama 12/02/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Western Michigan 12/16/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Minnesota 1/04/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Iowa 1/06/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Ohio State 1/20/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Michigan State 1/25/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Indiana 2/01/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)